<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
	<title>My Website</title>
	<link>https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/favorite-book-quotes/</link>
	<description>Recent content in Favorite-Book-Quotes on My Website</description>
	<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 14:56:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/favorite-book-quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	
	
	<item>
		<title>Blood Meridian</title>
		<link>https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/favorite-book-quotes/blood-meridian/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 14:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/favorite-book-quotes/blood-meridian/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Neighbors, said the reverend, he couldn’t stay out of these here hell, hell, hellholes right here in Nacogdoches. I said to him, said: You goin to take the son of God in there with ye? And he said: Oh no. No I ain’t. And I said: Dont you know that he said I will foller ye always even unto the end of the road?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, he said, I ain’t askin nobody to go nowheres. And I said: Neighbor, you dont need to ask. He’s a goin to be there with ye ever step of the way whether ye ask it or ye dont. I said: Neighbor, you caint get shed of him. Now. Are you going to drag him, him, into that hellhole yonder? You ever see such a place for rain?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/cowboy.png&#34; alt=&#34;cowboy&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a lone tree burning on the desert. A heraldic tree that the passing storm had left afire. The solitary pilgrim drawn up before it had traveled far to be here and he knelt in the hot sand and held his numbed hands out while all about in that circle attended companies of lesser auxiliaries routed forth into the inordinate day, small owls that crouched silently and stood from foot to foot and tarantulas and solpugas and vinegarroons and the vicious mygale spiders and beaded lizards with mouths black as a chowdog&amp;rsquo;s, deadly to man, and the little desert basilisks that jet blood from their eyes and the small sandvipers like seemly gods, silent and the same, in Jeda, in Babylon. A constellation of ignited eyes that edged the ring of light all bound in a precarious truce before this torch whose brightness had set back the stars in their sockets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://abrahamsandoval.xyz/burning_bush_night.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;burning bush&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>
